sup everyone tv5 you with a very
touchy-feely today today I'm doing some
special extra special I mean you
know what's up
but I'm doing a full review of like
snaps snacks appetizers mozzarella
sticks and cuz like I've never had
it so I'm gonna review that as you
all know because I'm the number-one
soccer fan in the world I also got a
blue cup of apple juice like well you
can't see it that to happen each other's
ears although it's a key yellow to you
know represent bowel be like Bobby is
like yellow and talk is blue so it's
like by dark and and the reason
it's like apple juice a look of it's
like you know I like Bobby shoving up
socks ass and right anyways let's dig
into this so I was like - called
always piss you might be wondering why
like the cheese and like not fill
out over the wall it was like cooking
the that's because my mom was
stupid I guess and get watch it anyways
yeah I'm gonna take another bow look at
like no cheese in that look at
that that's stupid look at that
look at that look look
that's Reb I need to wash it down
with that down with that Balaban piss
oh yeah that's the you you know
I'm gonna tell you a story today I want
you like this really oh I don't
know what how would you like the third
sonship well I created you like a -
oxfam no no I mean it was a kid who
wasn't a fan of Manning he was like
a fan of me George my videos and I said
cool do your parents like my videos and
he was like no my parents they are
modern France I was like that
sucks and he was like yeah they just to
show me and because they found out
I'm a model because they felt like suck
on them
that's the problem with my entire fangs
you know you pick it up what I'm putting
down come on exams out
like they don't know they don't know
what's up like they know B is locking
their asses and chair I'm here I'm good
so yeah and that was like my weekend
what about you these are pretty
good
I'm one more to keep my mama took their
ass if you want one
I'm saying for don't worry about what
should I write these I guess
I'll give it I'll give it Barbie
spanking songs as five times out of five
that's a perfect score